Contact

614.546.8412 (Mobile) danluk1311@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/danluk1311 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

User Experience (UX)
Communication
360 Feedback

Dan Luk

Software Developer

Bloomington, Indiana, United States

Summary

I am looking to transition into the tech industry. I have always been interested in solving problems using computers. I would like to expand my skills and knowledge in the tech industry. There are real people who are unaware of how their lives can be better through better applications. I would like to learn and use my skills to reach these people and show them how their lives can improve.

I have started with the Codecademy bootcamp and learned the following:

Javascript

HTML/CSS

SQL

React

Python

Experience

Reliant Mission

Pastor

Reliant Mission Field Staff

June 2009 - Present (13 years 10 months)

The Ohio State University
Research Associate
June 2006 - October 2009 (3 years 5 months)

Education

The Ohio State University

Master of Engineering - MEng, Aerospace, Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering · (September 2006 - December 2008)

Trinity Evangelical Divinity School

Master's degree, Theology/Theological Studies · (June 2014 - December 2017)

The Ohio State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Aerospace, Aeronautical and Astronautical

Engineering · (September 2002 - December 2008)